<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Wyzurd</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Wyzurd</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.140.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 10:40:52 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cam Creux iPad Mod</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/250121_camcreuxipadmod/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 10:40:52 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/250121_camcreuxipadmod/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m almost finished with modding my iPad mini with Cam Creux&amp;rsquo;s excellent &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.camcreux.com/product-page/spudnik-ipad-mod#&#34;&gt;netbridge mod&lt;/a&gt;. I started this in October but was pulled away by fatherhood and the chaos that comes with it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This time I reprinted the case in PETG (previously in ASA) and I&amp;rsquo;ve soldered together the gold mount plate so that the ipad can run forrrrevvverrrrr.  I&amp;rsquo;m using a &lt;a href=&#34;https://cinemilled.com/p/core-swx-nano-micro-50-lithium-ion-battery-gold-mount/?srsltid=AfmBOoqI_pvSaxJvSr53Xl_WosdZiaf3-LqE66j1BJMNsb0mZS9SEjkR&#34;&gt;super tiny gold mount battery&lt;/a&gt; by Core SWX.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those of you that don&amp;rsquo;t know, netbridge is a point to point 802.11ah chipset that allows a 1 to 4 communication.  It runs on the 900mhz frequency, meaning it goes a real long way (by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.makeyourown.lol/learn/projects/teehee-halow/halow-range/&#34;&gt;Sam Petrov&amp;rsquo;s testing&lt;/a&gt;, the netbridge goes 580ft in the open).  Also due to it&amp;rsquo;s lower frequency, the 900mhz can easily punch through concrete and other walls.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blackmagic Killed my Ultrastudio</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/blackmagickilledmyultrastudio3g/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 22:07:04 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/blackmagickilledmyultrastudio3g/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, it finally happened. Blackmagic has killed my Ultrastudio 3G with Thunderbolt 2.  They had Apple&amp;rsquo;s help with their new driver managment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you didn&amp;rsquo;t know, the decklink drivers on MacOS Sequoia is new a &amp;ldquo;Camera Driver&amp;rdquo;, and for whatever reason that seems to be causing a lot of issues for people with older ultrastudio hardware.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This happened right when I was starting a monitor calibration for Rushlight Studios, which made a simple job a bit of a pain. Fortunately I had purchased an AJA io4k over the summer since I was so impressed with AJA&amp;rsquo;s performance in Assimilate Scratch, and another bout of good fortune, Assimilate Scratch is compatible with my monitor calibration software (Colourspace) as a signal generator! So no hard feeling Blackmagic.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Website, Who Dis?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/250117/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 10:41:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/250117/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Check out the new site! It&amp;rsquo;s simple, it&amp;rsquo;s clean, its&amp;hellip;free?  That&amp;rsquo;s right! I&amp;rsquo;m using the CMS &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt; to create a dead simple site that&amp;rsquo;s managed with markdown files on github.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why am I doing this? Well to save money obviously. And I really just wanted a website that was deconstructed, and looked a bit more like a notion document.  Hopefully I&amp;rsquo;m lowering the upkeep and making it easier to update in the process.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ai Headshots</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2025-01-23-ai-headshots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2025-01-23-ai-headshots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I figured it was time to refresh my social media presence in the gig space (LinkedIn) and I realized I&amp;rsquo;m usually the guy behind the camera.  Not only that, but now that I have two kids, I just don&amp;rsquo;t have the time to set up a photo shoot for myself.  So I did what any responsible American did in the year 2025, I turned to ai.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did a little bit of research of the many many many ai headshots websites that are out there, and really couldn&amp;rsquo;t sift out what was good what was bad.  Ultimately I ended up just following a reddit post asking for reccomendations and saw the owner of proshoot.co piped in.  I figured, if this guy is passionate enough to post in the reddits, I&amp;rsquo;ll give it a chance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
